{
    "subject": "resource/James_Cronin",
    "predicate": "property/knownFor",
    "object": "resource/Nuclear_physics",
    "human_readable": "James Cronin is known for Nuclear physics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7632858753204346,
            "question": "What is James Cronin famous for researching?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7558724880218506,
            "question": "Who is known for their contributions to Nuclear physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6705235242843628,
            "question": "Name a scientist known for their work in Nuclear physics."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6446588635444641,
            "question": "What field is James Cronin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45065081119537354,
            "question": "What scientific field is associated with James Cronin's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.449726402759552,
            "question": "To which scientific field does James Cronin belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44088444113731384,
            "question": "In which scientific discipline did James Cronin make significant contributions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4279819130897522,
            "question": "What area of science did James Cronin specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34368106722831726,
            "question": "What is James Cronin's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33059075474739075,
            "question": "What is James Cronin's primary research focus?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Cronin is known for Nuclear physics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5745_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is James Cronin's area of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5745_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What area of science did James Cronin specialize in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5745_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which scientific discipline did James Cronin make significant contributions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5745_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5745_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's my evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nMy reasoning is as follows:\n\n* All the documents mention James Cronin as a nuclear physicist, with one document specifically mentioning him as an American nuclear physicist.\n* The documents also mention his research and discoveries related to physics, such as the discovery of CP-violation, which further supports his association with nuclear physics.\n\nTherefore, based on the information provided in the context, it is reasonable to conclude that James Cronin is indeed known for Nuclear physics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"James Cronin is known for Nuclear physics.\" They describe his work as an American nuclear physicist, his PhD in nuclear research, and his Nobel Prize-winning experiments related to subatomic particles and nuclear physics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}